<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<labels>
	<entry key='database.repair_colony_buildings'>Repairing colony buildings</entry>
	<entry key='database.battleship_production'>Producing battleships</entry>
	<entry key='database.deploy_starbase'>Deploying space stations</entry>
	<entry key='database.moral_boosting'>Improving colony morale</entry>
	<entry key='database.effective_spacewar'>Effective space battle strategies</entry>
	<entry key='database.effective_groudwar'>Effective ground battle strategies</entry>
	<entry key='database.spaceship_equipping'>Equipping spaceships</entry>
	<entry key='database.research_labs'>Role of development centers</entry>
	<entry key='database.tax_income'>Tax income</entry>
	<entry key='database.discovering_planets'>Information on planets</entry>
	
	<entry key='database.repair_colony_buildings.details'>On colonies, damaged buildings become less effective, e.g. If a Food farm is damaged, people will get less food, morale will drop and eventually your tax level will decrease. You may repair buildings by clicking on them, a panel will open at the top-right corner. If you click on the damage % icon, it will change to repair %. If a building is being repaired, you will see the damage number on it flashing as the repair is being done and the damage percentage decreasing.</entry>
	<entry key='database.battleship_production.details'>In order to produce larger ships, you need to build an orbital space factory as larger ships must be assembled in space. First, you need to develop the orbital space factory. When it has been developed, start production. Once a factory is produced, go to the equipment screen and click on a planet (in the small starmap). Once you have selected the planet, click on the space stations icon (bottom left hand corner). Click on the Orbital Space Factory, and click on the Add icon to equip the planet with the station.</entry>
	<entry key='database.deploy_starbase.details'>Once a space station is produced, go to the equipment screen and click on a planet (in the small starmap). Once you have selected the planet, click on the space stations icon (bottom left hand corner). Click on the selected space station, and click on the Add icon to equip the planet with the new station.</entry>
	<entry key='database.moral_boosting.details'>On all of the colonies, morale affects your population, growth and tax income. On human colonies, there are special buildings that increase morale, such as the Bar, Recreation Center, Park, Church and Stadium. It is up to you to discover the most effective way to increase morale. Taxation morale can also be raised by building Police Stations.
	Morale does not change rapidly and you may have to wait some time for your actions to take effect. Morale can also be increased by lowering tax for a while, and then increasing it slightly when the morale level is stable.
	On alien colonies, you cannot build parks or other "morale-increasing" buildings, but the police will help you. When you take over another race's colony, the alien population will hate you. Lowering their tax and building police stations to maintain order will change their attitude. Bear in mind, that morale does not change quickly.</entry>
	<entry key='database.effective_spacewar.details'>Use the pause function frequently (SPACE). Take your time to decide who you attack and with what. Flagships have large shields, but are slow. Try and refrain from sending them to different locations. You can select groups as well by clicking the left mouse button and dragging. Use SHIFT + numbers to create groups. You may reselect these groups by pressing the numbers, e.g. SHIFT 1 will create group 1, SHIFT 2 group 2. If you press 1, then group 1 will be selected. Flagships can be equipped with rockets that are quite useful against other spaceships, and bombs that can be used to bombard planetary defense systems. Since flagships are the only spaceships capable of carrying ground forces, one way to stop attempts to invade your colonies is to destroy the flagships before they reach your planet. Once all the flagships are destroyed, the ground forces they possessed will also have been disposed of.</entry>
	<entry key='database.effective_groudwar.details'>Use the pause function frequently (SPACE). Take your time to decide who you attack and with what. You can select groups by clicking the left mouse button and dragging. Use SHIFT + numbers to create groups. You may reselect these groups by pressing the numbers, e.g. SHIFT 1 will create group 1, SHIFT 2 group 2. If you press 1, then group 1 will be selected. When you attack or defend a colony, first you have to deploy your units. You must place them on the green squares. If you are attacking, you will start from the edge of the map. If you are defending your colony, you will be able to place units near your buildings. If you attack, some of the buildings will fire at you automatically (Garrisons, Fortresses, etc.). Avoid them if possible.</entry>
	<entry key='database.spaceship_equipping.details'>Each Cruiser, Destroyer and Flagship can be equipped with several items. Fighters cannot be equipped with weapons or other equipment. The larger a ship is, the more equipment can be fitted. If you click on a ship from your fleet, it can be equipped in the right window, where the key equipment areas or bays are marked with a green square. Click on the green square, and you will be able to choose from the items you can add, e.g. if you have 10 laser 1.0 equipped and the maximum you can have is 14, click on the +1 button to add laser 1.0 from your stock to the equip bay. This way, you may add 4 more until the maximum amount is reached.
	You can use the equipment bays for the same type of weapons as well, e.g. if an equipped part of the ship has laser 1.0, and you have laser 2.0 in stock, you will first have to remove laser 1.0 from the equip bay in order to replace it with laser 2.0. This may require a bit of a work but it's well worth it. If your equipment pod has laser 1.0, that means you can use that space to add laser type weapons only. You cannot add radars or any other weapon type to the equipment pod that supports lasers.
	In order to equip items to your ship, you need to be near one of your planets which has a military spaceport built on it. This spaceport provides short range transfer ships which will transport the items from your stock pile to the spaceship and equip them. Some spaceships come with standard equipment, like hyperdrives. These come as standard with the ship. They cannot be removed and you cannot equip any other items to this bay.
	When your spaceship gets damaged, the equipment parts also sustain damage. In this instance the green squares representing the equipment pods will turn yellow for (medium damage) or red (heavy damage). When bays are damaged, the equipment in the bay is also damaged, e.g. you may lose equipped laser cannons due to sustained hits. That is why it is important to check your spaceship's equipment after battle. The damaged parts will repair after some time but if you lose weapons, you will need to re-equip them.</entry>
	<entry key='database.research_labs.details'>Most research options are linked to technology levels. The technology levels are split into 5 areas: Civil Engineering, Mechanics, Computer Technology, Artificial Intelligence and Military Technology. Your capabilities in these five areas are determined by the type and number of Development Centers you have. Each planet you control may only have one development center so you will need to plan carefully in which area to increase. N.B. Your technology levels are only increased if the development centers you have are fully functioning.
	If a center has over 50% damage, or has no electricity/power the additional benefits will be lost. If you demolish a development center, your technology in that field will also decrease. This is how you can develop new inventions using your planets' resources. If you have 1-Civil Engineering and 2-Military Dev.Centers, and need 2-Civil Engineering and 1-Military Dev.Center to create an invention, you can simply demolish one of your Military Dev.Centers and build a Civil Engineering center on that planet.</entry>
	<entry key='database.tax_income.details'>Your finances depend solely on tax and trade income. Trade income is a long term investment, while tax income will be your main source of earning. Trade income gives you 600 credits/day, if you own a Traders space port. Trade Center creates an income of 1200 credits/day. If you have a bank on the colony, the bank will double all the trade income. Tax income depends on several factors:
	- the number of people living on the planet,
	- the taxation level (controlled by you),
	- taxation morale
	
	If the taxation level is high, (demanding and opressive) it is very likely that the population will be unhappy. The taxation morale will decrease and unrest will spread throughout the colony. On special occasions you may still use high taxation levels, but this cannot be used as a long term strategy. Taxation morale can be increased in several ways. Trade income does not depend on tax morale so it can be used effectively on alien planets to create a stable source of income. Keeping the taxes low will also make the inhabitants feel more secure.</entry>
	<entry key='database.discovering_planets.details'>It is very important to obtain information about planets. If a planet's name is not visible, it means you have not established contact with the planet. It could be empty, or have alien colonies on it. 
	First, you need to deploy a satellite to establish contact and retrieve vital statistics, e.g. if the planet is habitable or not. If you have a SAT in stock and click on an empty planet on the starmap you can deploy it by clicking on the add sat icon. It will soon start to relay information on the planet.
	The information relay will become more substantial as time progresses. If the planet is already inhabited, the satellite may be spotted, and destroyed. The next step would be to deploy a spy satellite. Spy sat 2.0 will relay more information and enable you spy on the alien race's colony of buildings when you select a planet. It will also relay information about the planetary defence forces.</entry>
	
	<entry key='database.race.freetraders'>Free Traders Alliance</entry>
	<entry key='database.race.freenations'>Free Nations Society</entry>
	<entry key='database.race.pirates'>Pirates</entry>
	<entry key='database.race.garthog'>Garthogs</entry>
	<entry key='database.race.ychom'>Ychoms</entry>
	<entry key='database.race.morgath'>Morgaths</entry>
	<entry key='database.race.dribs'>Dribs</entry>
	<entry key='database.race.ecalep'>Ecaleps</entry>
	<entry key='database.race.sullep'>Sulleps</entry>
	<entry key='database.race.dargslan'>Dargslans</entry>
	
	<entry key='database.race.freetraders.details'>Once part of the Old Empire, the traders left to create a new empire for themselves. They are a peaceful race of traders and enjoy good relations with the Ychoms</entry>
	<entry key='database.race.freenations.details'>Once part of the Old Empire, they declared themselves independent a long time ago. The Free Nations Society has developed rapidly, occupying territories with ease. The Society is well known for their arrogant attitude and contempt for the Empire.</entry>
	<entry key='database.race.pirates.details'>The Pirates are a bunch of outlaws coming from multiple races. They prefer attacking defenseless trade ships and colonies lost all their morale may likely to join them. They have, so far, never attacked a military fleet deliberately.</entry>
	<entry key='database.race.garthog.details'>The Garthogs are a contemptible and un-trustworthy race, who implant their young with bio-mechanical devices. They have a special interest in mechanics and are renowned for stealing the technology of other races. It is rumored that they destroyed and entire race, known as the Nubs, to obtain their secrets. The Garthog Empire is close to the Human Empire and there has been conflict for 10 years. The Garthogs possess a special ground weapon: the radar jammer vehicle.</entry>
	<entry key='database.race.ychom.details'>A Peaceful, trader race. That enjoys good relations with the Free Traders Alliance. Ychoms have a unique way of defending their colonies: each has a mine-deploying saucer.</entry>
	<entry key='database.race.morgath.details'>The Morgaths are an insular and hostile race. It is rumored that they have powerful spaceships and a special ground weapon: a kamikaze tank. This weapon should be avoided at all costs!</entry>
	<entry key='database.race.dribs.details'>The Dribs are a proud race with advanced technology, especially in the fields of mechanics and architecture. They have known of the Dargslan race for a long time, since the Dargslans occupied some Drib territory. Since then, they have hated the Dargslan race.</entry>
	<entry key='database.race.ecalep.details'>With the rapid expansion of their empire, tax revenue has increased to a very high level. This partially explains their obsession with money. They have developed a new ground weapon called the anti-missile tank, which is immune to rocket launchers.</entry>
	<entry key='database.race.sullep.details'>The Sulleps' are a walike race with a very strict social structure. From a very young age, Sulleps' are subjected to military training. Such is their code of combat, it is more honourable for them to die in battle than surrender.</entry>
	<entry key='database.race.dargslan.details'>Very little is known about the Dargslans. Intelligence reports show that they have extremely powerful ground attack forces, as well as a competent space fleet.</entry>

	<entry key='database.map.1'>
	
	1. Bridge
	2. Lieutenant's room
	3. Crew quarters
	</entry>
	<entry key='database.map.2'>
	1. Híd
	2. Commander's room
	3. Crew quarters
	4. Bar
	</entry>
	<entry key='database.map.3'>
	
	1. Bridge
	2. Research-production terminals
	3. Equipment terminal
	4. Captain's room
	5. Bar
	6. Crew quarters 
	</entry>
	<entry key='database.map.4'>
	
	1. Bridge
	2. Research-production terminals
	3. Equipment terminal
	4. Admiral's room
	5. Bar
	6. Crew quarters 
	7. Diplomatic relations room
	</entry>
	<entry key='database.map.5'>
	
	1. Bridge
	2. Research-production terminals
	3. Equipment terminal
	4. Fleet Admiral's room
	5. Bar
	6. Crew quarters 
	7. Diplomatic relations room
	</entry>
	<entry key='database.map.1.title'>The Destroyer's map</entry>
	<entry key='database.map.2.title'>The Cruiser's map</entry>
	<entry key='database.map.3.title'>The Thorin flagship's map</entry>
	<entry key='database.map.4.title'>The Thorin flagship's map</entry>
	<entry key='database.map.5.title'>The Thorin flagship's map</entry>
	
	<entry key='bar.phsychologist.101'>Hello Doctor. Do You have some time for me?</entry>
	<entry key='bar.phsychologist.111'>I'd like You to tell me about the test I had to complete.</entry>
	<entry key='bar.phsychologist.112'>I have some dreams which need rectification...</entry>
	<entry key='bar.phsychologist.121'>Thank You for Your time. I have to go now.</entry>
	
	<entry key='bar.brian.301'>Hey Brian! Aren't You a little young for a head-tech?</entry>
	<entry key='bar.brian.311'>Didn't know I have to do with a military tech-expert...</entry>
	<entry key='bar.brian.312'>Do you think there is still a robot research going on?</entry>
	<entry key='bar.brian.321'>Tell me, how does this kind of research happen?</entry>
	<entry key='bar.brian.323'>Why did You leave development?</entry>
	<entry key='bar.brian.331'>Thank You for Your help. Enjoy your leave, Brian.</entry>
	
	<entry key='bar.kelly.001'>Greetings, Kelly. What's up?</entry>
	<entry key='bar.kelly.011'>I see you don't really like these situations.</entry>
	<entry key='bar.kelly.021'>What do you mean?</entry>
	<entry key='bar.kelly.022'>Do you think an alien could have slipped onto the ship?</entry>
	<entry key='bar.kelly.032'>Look, I saw someone running out of my room, which was a mess.</entry>
	<entry key='bar.kelly.041'>Thank you for you advice, Kelly.</entry>
	
	<entry key='bar.doctor.401'>Greetings doctor. What's the situation?</entry>
	<entry key='bar.doctor.402'>Relaxing, doc?</entry>
	<entry key='bar.doctor.411'>As I know You understand robots?</entry>
	<entry key='bar.doctor.412'>As I know You worked on robotics earlier, aren't you?</entry>
	<entry key='bar.doctor.421'>I'm interested in the research going on Earth.</entry>
	<entry key='bar.doctor.431'>I think I need to speak with him. Can you help me?</entry>
	<entry key='bar.doctor.441'>I must speak with the professor. It's very important..</entry>
	<entry key='bar.doctor.451'>Thank you doc. You helped me a lot.</entry>
	
	<entry key='mainmenu.singleplayer'>Single player</entry>
	<entry key='mainmenu.continue'>Continue</entry>
	<entry key='mainmenu.load'>Load</entry>
	<entry key='mainmenu.multiplayer'>Multiplayer</entry>
	<entry key='mainmenu.settings'>Settings</entry>
	<entry key='mainmenu.videos'>Videos</entry>
	<entry key='mainmenu.videos.intro'>Intro</entry>
	<entry key='mainmenu.videos.title'>Title</entry>
	<entry key='mainmenu.exit'>Exit</entry>
	<entry key='EN'>EN</entry>
	<entry key='HU'>HU</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.conqueror">Conqueror</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.conqueror.desc">Conquered the first enemy planet</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.millionaire">Millionaire</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.millionaire.desc">You collected 1.000.000 credits</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.student_of_bokros">Student of Bokros</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.student_of_bokros.desc">All your planets sustained the Oppressive taxation for a week</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.pirate_bay">Pirate Bay</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.pirate_bay.desc">You lost a planet to the Pirates</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.dargslayer">Dargslayer</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.dargslayer.desc">You eliminated all Dargslan from the galaxy</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.energizer">Energizer</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.energizer.desc">Your total energy production reached 10.000.000 kW</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.death_star">Death Star</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.death_star.desc">You left your colony to be destroyed</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.research_assistant">Research assistant</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.research_assistant.desc">You researched 5 technologies</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.scientist">Scientist</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.scientist.desc">You researched 30 technologies</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.nobel_prize">Nobel prize</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.nobel_prize.desc">You researched all technologies</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.popular">Popular</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.popular.desc">All your colonies are happy with you</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.apeh">Happy clients of APEH</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.apeh.desc">All your colonies have above 95% tax morale</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.ultimate_leader">Ultimate leader</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.ultimate_leader.desc">All your colonies support you</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.revolutioner">Revolutioner</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.revolutioner.desc">One of your colony has revolved</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.mass_effect">Mass effect</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.mass_effect.desc">Your total population got above 1.000.000</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.defender">Defender of the crown</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.defender.desc">You successfully defended your colony</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.embargo">Embargo</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.embargo.desc">You destroyed your first Trader ship</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.colombus">Colombus</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.colombus.desc">You colonized your first planet</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.quarter">Quarter of the pie</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.quarter.desc">You own 25 planets</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.manufacturer">Manufacturer</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.manufacturer.desc">You produced a total of 1.000 items</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.salvage">Salvage</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.salvage.desc">You destroyed 1.000 enemy ships</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.living_space">Living space</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.living_space.desc">You discovered your first empty planet.</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.food">Food for thought</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.food.desc">Your food production is above 1.000.000</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.decade">A decade in the service</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.decade.desc">You played 10 game years</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.oldest_man">Oldest man</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.oldest_man.desc">You played 100 game years</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.all_your_base">All your base are belong to us</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.all_your_base.desc">Your enemies captured one of your planets</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.et">E.T. exists</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.et.desc">You discovered a non-human civilization</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.defense_contract">Defense contract</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.defense_contract.desc">All your planets are equipped with at least 3 planetary guns and one shield.</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.coffee_break">Coffee break</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.coffee_break.desc">You paused your game for 30 minutes</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.all_seeing_eye">All seeing eye</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.all_seeing_eye.desc">At least 80% of the galaxy is covered by radar</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.newbie">Newbie</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.newbie.desc">Started a new game</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.commander">Commander</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.commander.desc">You have been promoted to commander</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.admiral">Admiral</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.admiral.desc">You have been promoted to admiral</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.grand_admiral">Grand Admiral</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.grand_admiral.desc">You have been promoted to grand admiral</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.influenza">Influenza no more</entry>
	<entry key="achievement.influenza.desc">You successfully eliminated the source of the virus infection</entry>
	<entry key='achievements'>Achievements</entry>
	<entry key='statistics'>Statistics</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.total_gametime'>Real time spent</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.total_ingame_time'>Game time spent</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.money_aquired'>Money income</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.money_aquired_trade'>Money income from trade</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.money_spent'>Money spent</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.money_spent_building'>Money spent on buildings</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.money_spent_production'>Money spent on production</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.money_spent_research'>Money spent on research</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.equipment_sold_money'>Money got on selling</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.planet_discovered'>Planets discovered</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.planet_own'>Palnets own</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.planet_colonized'>Planets colonized</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.races_discovered'>Planets discovered</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.produced_items'>Items produced</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.sold_items'>Items sold</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.research_count'>Research count</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.research_acquired'>Research acquired</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.total_population'>Total population</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.total_houses'>Total housing capacity</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.total_energy'>Total energy production</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.total_energy_demand'>Total energy demand</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.total_buildings'>Total building count</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.actual_buildings'>Operational building count</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.total_food_production'>Total food production</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.total_hospital'>Total hospital coverage</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.total_worker'>Total worker demand</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.total_police'>Total police coverage</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.total_fleet'>Total fleet count</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.total_own_firepower'>Total own firepower</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.total_enemy_firepower'>Total enemy firepower</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.ships_destroyed'>Ships destroyed</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.ships_destroyed_value'>Value of ships destroyed.</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_money_acquired'>Galaxy money acquired</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_money_spent'>Galaxy money spent</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_total_population'>Galaxy total population</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_total_buildings'>Galaxy total buildings</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_total_houses'>Galaxy total housing capacity</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_total_energy'>Galaxy total energy production</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_total_energy_demand'>Galaxy total energy demand</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_total_worker'>Galaxy total worker demand</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_total_food'>Galaxy total food production</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_total_hospital'>Galaxy total hospital coverage</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_total_police'>Galaxy total police coverage</entry>
	<entry key='videos.path'>Category</entry>
	<entry key='videos.name'>Name</entry>
	<entry key='videos.play'>Play</entry>
	<entry key='videos.back'>Back</entry>
	<entry key='videos.all_videos'>All videos</entry>
	<entry key='singleplayer.start_game'>Start Game</entry>
	<entry key='singleplayer.back'>Back</entry>
	<entry key='singleplayer.difficulty'>Difficulty</entry>
	<entry key='difficulty.easy'>Easy</entry>
	<entry key='difficulty.normal'>Normal</entry>
	<entry key='difficulty.hard'>Hard</entry>
	<entry key='singleplayer.campaigns'>Campaigns</entry>
	<entry key='singleplayer.description'>Description</entry>
	<entry key='loading'>Loading</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.show_hide_buildings'>Show/hide buildings</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.object_placement_mode'>Object placement mode</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.symbolic_buildings'>Minimap rendering mode</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.view_text_background'>Show/hide text background boxes</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.place_roads'>Place roads</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.file'>File</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.edit'>Edit</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.view'>View</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.help'>Help</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.file_new'>New...</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.file_open'>Open...</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.file_import'>Import...</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.file_save'>Save</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.file_save_as'>Save as...</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.file_exit'>Exit</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.edit_undo'>Undo</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.edit_redo'>Redo</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.edit_cut'>Cut</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.edit_copy'>Copy</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.edit_paste'>Paste</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.edit_delete_building'>Delete building</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.edit_delete_surface'>Delete surface</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.edit_delete_both'>Delete both</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.edit_clear_buildings'>Clear buildings</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.edit_clear_surface'>Clear surface</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.view_zoom_in'>Zoom in</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.view_zoom_out'>Zoom out</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.view_zoom_normal'>Zoom normal</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.view_bright'>Daylight (1.0)</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.view_dark'>Night (0.5)</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.view_more_light'>More light (+0.05)</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.view_less_light'>Less light (-0.05)</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.help_online'>Online help...</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.help_about'>About</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.language_en'>English</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.language_hu'>Hungarian</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.language'>Language</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.apply'>Apply</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.refresh'>Refresh</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.allocation_available_workers'>Available workers:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.allocation_available_energy'>Available energy:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.allocation_strategies'>Strategies:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.allocation_energy_demand'>Energy demand:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.allocation_worker_demand'>Worker demand:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.allocation_operation_count'>Operational:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.allocation_total_efficiency'>Total efficiency:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.enabled'>Enabled</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.repairing'>Repairing</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.resource'>Resource</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.amount'>Amount</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.info_completed'>Completed:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.info_hitpoints'>Hitpoints:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.info_worker'>Worker:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.info_energy'>Energy:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.info_building_name'>Building name:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.info_completed_of'> of </entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.info_hitpoints_of'> of </entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.info_worker_of'> of </entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.info_energy_of'> of </entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.info_efficiency'>Efficiency:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.info_technology'>Technology:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.info_cost'>Cost:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.info_location'>Location:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.info_upgrade'>Upgrades:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.surface_and_buildings'>Surfaces &amp; Buildings</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.building_properties'>Building properties</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.allocation'>Allocation</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.tile_preview'>Preview</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.tile_size'>Size</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.tile_name'>Name</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.tile_surface'>Surface</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.tile_race'>Race</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.filter_surface'>Filter by size, name and surface. Example: '1x earth' means search for tiles with width=1 and surface=earth</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.filter_building'>Filter by size, name and race. Example: '2x human' means search for tiles with width=2 and race=human</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.preview_brightness'>Adjust brightness level. Buildings should turn on lights below 51 by default.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.offline'>OFFLINE</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.colony_hub'>Colony Hub</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.prefab_housing'>Prefab Housing</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.apartment_block'>Apartment Block</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.arcology'>Arcology</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.nuclear_plant'>Nuclear Plant</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.fusion_plant'>Fusion Plant</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.solar_plant'>Solar Plant</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.water_vaporator'>Water Vaporator</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.hydroponic_food_farm'>Hydroponic Food Farm</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.phood_factory'>Phood Factory</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.spaceship_factory'>Spaceship Factory</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.equipment_factory'>Equipment Factory</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.weapon_factory'>Weapon Factory</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.civil_dev_center'>Civil Dev Center</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.mechanical_dev_center'>Mechanical Dev Center</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.computer_dev_center'>Computer Dev Center</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.ai_dev_center'>AI Dev Center</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.military_dev_center'>Military Dev Center</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.traders_spaceport'>Traders Spaceport</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.military_spaceport'>Military Spaceport</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.bank'>Bank</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.trade_center'>Trade Center</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.hospital'>Hospital</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.police_station'>Police Station</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.fire_brigade'>File Brigade</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.radar_telescope'>Radar Telescope</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.field_telescope'>Field Telescope</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.phased_telescope'>Phased Telescope</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.bunker'>Bunker</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.ion_projector'>Ion Projector</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.plasma_projector'>Plasma Projector</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.fusion_projector'>Fusion Projector</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.meson_projector'>Meson Projector</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.inversion_shield'>Inversion Shield</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.hypershield'>Hypershield</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.barracks'>Barracks</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.fortress'>Fortress</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.stronghold'>Stronghold</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.recreation_center'>Recreation Center</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.park'>Park</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.church'>Church</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.bar'>Bar</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.stadium'>Stadium</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.save_map'>Save map</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.load_map'>Load map</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.save_surface_features'>Save surface features</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.load_surface_features'>Load surface features</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.save_buildings'>Save buildings</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.load_buildings'>Load buildings</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.browse'>Browse...</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.save_map_save'>Save</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.open_map_open'>Open</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.cancel'>Cancel</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.import_title'>Import a map or planet settings</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.import_nothing'>-Don't import any-</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.import_original_map'>Original map:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.import_shift_x'>Shift X:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.import_shift_y'>Shift Y:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.import_original_planet'>Original planet:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.import_replace_surface'>Replace current surface</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.import_replace_buildings'>Replace current buildings</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.import_import'>Import</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.import_replace_both'>Replace surface along with the buildings</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.filename'>File name:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.recent'>Recent</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.clear_recent'>Clear recent</entry>
	
	<entry key='mapeditor.edit_resize'>Resize map...</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.edit_cleanup'>Remove outbound objects</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.new_map'>New Map</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.resize_map'>Resize Map</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.new_width'>Width:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.new_height'>Height:</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.ok'>OK</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.cleanup_result'>Cleanup results: Total = %d, Buildings = %d, Surfaces = %d</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.view_standard_fonts'>Use standard fonts</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.view_placement_hints'>View placement hints</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.edit_cut_building'>Cut: building</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.edit_cut_surface'>Cut: surface</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.edit_copy_building'>Copy: building</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.edit_copy_surface'>Copy: surface</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.edit_paste_building'>Paste: building</entry>
	<entry key='mapeditor.edit_paste_surface'>Paste: surface</entry>
	<entry key='equipment.spaceships'>Ships   :%d</entry>
	<entry key='equipment.fighters'>Fighters:%d</entry>
	<entry key='equipment.vehicles'>Vehicles:%d</entry>
	<entry key='equipment.max'>max:%d</entry>
	<entry key='equipment.maxpertype'>max:%d/type</entry>
	<entry key='equipment.secondary'>Secondary:</entry>
	<entry key='equipment.vehiclesandmax'>Vehicles:%d/%d</entry>
	<entry key='equipment.innercount'>Act:%d Max:%d</entry>
	<entry key='equipment.selectednametype'>Name:%s   Type:%s</entry>
	<entry key='building.resource.type.energy'> kWh</entry>
	<entry key='building.resource.type.house'> men</entry>
	<entry key='building.resource.type.food'> t</entry>
	<entry key='building.resource.type.multiply'> x income</entry>
	<entry key='building.resource.type.credit'> cr</entry>
	<entry key='building.resource.type.hospital'> men</entry>
	<entry key='planets.earth'>Earth</entry>
	
	<entry key='players.empire'>Galactic Empire</entry>
	<entry key='players.free_traders'>Free Traders Alliance</entry>
	<entry key='players.free_nations'>Free Nations Society</entry>
	<entry key='players.pirates'>Pirates</entry>
	<entry key='players.garthog'>Garthog Republic</entry>
	<entry key='players.ychom'>Ychom Empire</entry>
	<entry key='players.morgath'>Morgath Empire</entry>
	<entry key='players.dribs'>Dribs Empire</entry>
	<entry key='players.ecalep'>Ecalep Republic</entry>
	<entry key='players.sullep'>Sullep Empire</entry>
	<entry key='players.dargslan'>Dargslan Kingdom</entry>

	<entry key='players.empire.short'>Empire</entry>
	<entry key='players.free_traders.short'>Free Traders</entry>
	<entry key='players.free_nations.short'>Free Nations</entry>
	<entry key='players.pirates.short'>Pirates</entry>
	<entry key='players.garthog.short'>Garthog</entry>
	<entry key='players.ychom.short'>Ychom</entry>
	<entry key='players.morgath.short'>Morgath</entry>
	<entry key='players.dribs.short'>Dribs</entry>
	<entry key='players.ecalep.short'>Ecalep</entry>
	<entry key='players.sullep.short'>Sullep</entry>
	<entry key='players.dargslan.short'>Dargslan</entry>
	
	<entry key='planet.type.rocky'>rocky</entry>
	<entry key='planet.type.cratered'>cratered</entry>
	<entry key='planet.type.earth'>Earth-like</entry>
	<entry key='planet.type.liquid'>liquid</entry>
	<entry key='planet.type.neptoplasm'>neptoplasm</entry>
	<entry key='planet.type.desert'>desert</entry>
	<entry key='planet.type.frozen'>frozen</entry>
	
	<entry key='morale.revolt'>revolt</entry>
	<entry key='morale.hate'>hate</entry>
	<entry key='morale.dislike'>dislike</entry>
	<entry key='morale.neutral'>neutral</entry>
	<entry key='morale.like'>like</entry>
	<entry key='morale.supportive'>supportive</entry>

	<entry key='taxlevel.NONE'>None</entry>
	<entry key='taxlevel.VERY_LOW'>Very low</entry>
	<entry key='taxlevel.LOW'>Low</entry>
	<entry key='taxlevel.MODERATE'>Moderate</entry>
	<entry key='taxlevel.ABOVE_MODERATE'>Above moderate</entry>
	<entry key='taxlevel.HIGH'>High</entry>
	<entry key='taxlevel.VERY_HIGH'>Very high</entry>
	<entry key='taxlevel.OPPRESSIVE'>Oppressive</entry>
	<entry key='taxlevel.EXPLOITER'>Exploiter</entry>
	<entry key='taxlevel.SLAVERY'>Slavery</entry>
	
	<entry key='colonyinfo.planet'    >Planet : %s</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.owner'     >Owner        : %s</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.race'      >Race         : %s</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.surface'   >Surface      : %s</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.population'>Population   : %d %s (%s)</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.population.alien'>Population   : %d alien</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.housing'   >Living space : %d / %d men</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.worker'    >Worker       : %d / %d men</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.hospital'  >Hospital     : %d / %d men</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.food'      >Food         : %d / %d men</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.energy'    >Energy       : %d / %d kWh</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.police'    >Police       : %d / %d lakos</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.tax-trade' >Tax : %d cr    Trade : %d cr</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.tax'       >Tax income   : %d cr</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.trade'     >Trade income : %d cr</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.tax-info'>Tax level : %s    Tax morale : %d%% (%s)</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.tax-morale'>Tax morale   : %d%% (%s)</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.tax-level' >Tax level    : %s</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.allocation'>Allocation   : %s</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.autobuild' >Auto-build   : %s</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.other'     >Other        : %s</entry>
	
	<entry key='race.human'>Human</entry>
	<entry key='race.garthog'>Garthog</entry>
	<entry key='race.morgath'>Morgath</entry>
	<entry key='race.sullep'>Sullep</entry>
	<entry key='race.ecalep'>Ecalep</entry>
	<entry key='race.ychom'>Ychom</entry>
	<entry key='race.dribs'>Dribs</entry>
	<entry key='race.dargslan'>Dargslan</entry>
	
	<entry key='autobuild.OFF'>Off</entry>
	<entry key='autobuild.CIVIL'>Civil buildings</entry>
	<entry key='autobuild.ECONOMIC'>Economic buildings</entry>
	<entry key='autobuild.FACTORY'>Factory buildings</entry>
	
	<entry key='allocation.ZERO'>None</entry>
	<entry key='allocation.DEFAULT'>Uniform</entry>
	<entry key='allocation.DAMAGE_AWARE'>Enhanced uniform</entry>
	
	<entry key='buildings.upgrade.default.description'>Restore to default level (e.g., the post build level).</entry>

	<entry key='tech.fighter1.name'>Fighter v1</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fighter1.longname'>Fighter 1: "Raptor"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fighter1.description'>The Raptor is a simple no-frills fighter craft. It is armed with dual laser cannons and has a low powered magnetic deflection shield for defense.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fighter2.name'>Fighter v2</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fighter2.longname'>Fighter 2: "Valkyrie"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fighter2.description'>The Valkyrie is a superior fighter to the Raptor in every respect. It has a quad laser battery for firepower, a higher gauss mag-def shield and more powerful drives.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fighter3.name'>Fighter v3</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fighter3.longname'>Fighter 3: "Hammerhead"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fighter3.description'>Carrying a dual twin laser weapons load the Hammerhead is an incremental improvement on the Valkyrie. It also has a new shield design with high capacity field inductors.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fighter4.name'>Fighter v4</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fighter4.longname'>Fighter 4: "Streak"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fighter4.description'>The Streak is a deadly craft, swift and lethal. 4 twin lasers, coupled with the most advanced drive tech available. When designed, it became a serious threat in combat.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fighter5.name'>Fighter v5</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fighter5.longname'>Fighter 5: "WraithFighter"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fighter5.description'>The WraithFighter utilizes advances in stealth technology combined with a new phase coupled dipole mag deflector shield array to achieve an almost unhittable fighter.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fighter6.name'>Fighter v6</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fighter6.longname'>Fighter 6: "Strikebomber"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fighter6.description'>The Strikebomber is a heavy craft designed for dropping unguided high yield bombs on heavy craft. It is a real threat but must have a fighter escort for optimal effect.</entry>
	
	<entry key='tech.destroyer1.name'>Destroyer v1</entry>
	<entry key='tech.destroyer1.longname'>Destroyer 1: "Guardian"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.destroyer1.description'>This is the most commonly encountered light destroyer. A leftover from the times of the Old Empire, its main advantage is its low cost and ready availability.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.destroyer2.name'>Destroyer v2</entry>
	<entry key='tech.destroyer2.longname'>Destroyer 2: "Warrior"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.destroyer2.description'>The Warrior Class are just refitted Guardian Class destroyers, well equipped with more modern weaponry, but still vulnerable due to a low power shield generator.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.destroyer3.name'>Destroyer v3</entry>
	<entry key='tech.destroyer3.longname'>Destroyer 3: "Jabberwocky"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.destroyer3.description'>The Jabberwocky Class is the pinnacle of destroyer development. Good shields, heavy firepower, and a dual magnetic ram-pump drive system for high speed and versatility.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.cruiser1.name'>Cruiser v1</entry>
	<entry key='tech.cruiser1.longname'>Cruiser 1: "Thunder"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.cruiser1.description'>Another leftover from the Old Empire, it is outdated but cheap and readily available.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.cruiser2.name'>Cruiser v2</entry>
	<entry key='tech.cruiser2.longname'>Cruiser 2: "Thunder-II"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.cruiser2.description'>The designers concentrated on the shield generators of this upgrade to the Thunder Class, but this additional mass without stronger drives made it a bit sluggish.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.cruiser3.name'>Cruiser v3</entry>
	<entry key='tech.cruiser3.longname'>Cruiser 3: "Cahudhri"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.cruiser3.description'>Advanced drive systems, coupled with heavier armor, and cutting edge targeting and fire control make this the most feared cruiser in the Empire's arsenal.</entry>
	
	<entry key='tech.battleship1.name'>Battleship v1</entry>
	<entry key='tech.battleship1.longname'>Battleship 1: "Mammoth"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.battleship1.description'>Powerful shields, heavy weaponry, and capable of carrying ground assault forces. Since these has to be built in space, an orbital factory is needed to produce them.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.battleship2.name'>Battleship v2</entry>
	<entry key='tech.battleship2.longname'>Battleship 2: "Python"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.battleship2.description'>A bit slower than the Mammoth, the Python's firepower is far superior. The ground unit payload has also been enlarged and its shields are much stronger.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.battleship3.name'>Battleship v3</entry>
	<entry key='tech.battleship3.longname'>Battleship 3: "Kraken"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.battleship3.description'>The Kraken has heavy shields, massive firepower, and the capability to land a fully equipped army on enemy worlds. The Kraken is the jewel of the Empire's fleets.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.colonyship.name'>Colony ship</entry>
	<entry key='tech.colonyship.longname'>Colonization ship</entry>
	<entry key='tech.colonyship.description'>The Colonization ship is used to establish colonies. These immense vessels carry construction tools, colonists, everything needed for a new start on a virgin planet.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.flagship.name'>Thorin</entry>
	<entry key='tech.flagship.longname'>Thorin</entry>
	<entry key='tech.flagship.description'>The Thorin is the only surviving Leviathan Class Flagship. It is significantly more powerful than the Kraken Class Flagship.</entry>
	
	<entry key='tech.satellite.name'>Survey Satellite</entry>
	<entry key='tech.satellite.longname'>Survey Satellite</entry>
	<entry key='tech.satellite.description'>The Survey Satellite is used to gather information on unexplored and unknown planets.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.spysatellite1.name'>Spy Satellite</entry>
	<entry key='tech.spysatellite1.longname'>Spy Satellite</entry>
	<entry key='tech.spysatellite1.description'>Spy Satellites are used to detect and monitor alien communications, activities and fleet movements.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.spysatellite2.name'>Adv. Spy Sat.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.spysatellite2.longname'>Advanced Spy Satellite</entry>
	<entry key='tech.spysatellite2.description'>This upgraded Spy Satellite has significant stealth enhancements and better sensors to detect and report on the ships and space bases around enemy planets.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.hubble2.name'>Hubble 2</entry>
	<entry key='tech.hubble2.longname'>Hubble 2</entry>
	<entry key='tech.hubble2.description'>A powerful Radar Telescope Satellite named after a famous Old Earth scientific satellite. The Hubble 2 can detect enemy fleets over very large distances.</entry>
	
	<entry key='tech.spacestation1.name'>Space Station 1</entry>
	<entry key='tech.spacestation1.longname'>Space Station 1: "Defender"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.spacestation1.description'>Space Stations are used to protect your planets from attack. They have heavy firepower and strong hull. They are the key to an effective defense.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.orbitalfactory.name'>Orbital Factory</entry>
	<entry key='tech.orbitalfactory.longname'>Orbital Factory</entry>
	<entry key='tech.orbitalfactory.description'>Orbital Factories provide the zero-g construction facilities needed to build your gigantic flagships.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.spacestation2.name'>Space Station 2</entry>
	<entry key='tech.spacestation2.longname'>Space Station 2: "Giant"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.spacestation2.description'>The Giant has massive firepower, and is capable of putting up a stiff resistance to enemy fleets that attempt to assault the planets it guards.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.spacestation3.name'>Space Station 3</entry>
	<entry key='tech.spacestation3.longname'>Space Station 3: "Colossus"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.spacestation3.description'>The Colossus is the largest of all defensive stations. It can be a formidable foe for even the largest of starships.</entry>
	
	<entry key='tech.hyperdrive1.name'>Hyperdrive v1</entry>
	<entry key='tech.hyperdrive1.longname'>Hyperdrive v1.0</entry>
	<entry key='tech.hyperdrive1.description'>This upgrades some of your spaceships. They will be able to travel 15% faster with this improved drive system.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.hyperdrive2.name'>Hyperdrive v2</entry>
	<entry key='tech.hyperdrive2.longname'>Hyperdrive v2.0</entry>
	<entry key='tech.hyperdrive2.description'>The upgraded spaceships will be able to travel 20% faster, with 15% less fuel consumption.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.hyperdrive3.name'>Hyperdrive v3</entry>
	<entry key='tech.hyperdrive3.longname'>Hyperdrive v3.0</entry>
	<entry key='tech.hyperdrive3.description'>This module upgrades your flagships. Two extra boosters help increase the speed of the ship by 22%.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.hyperdrive4.name'>Hyperdrive v4</entry>
	<entry key='tech.hyperdrive4.longname'>Hyperdrive v4.0</entry>
	<entry key='tech.hyperdrive4.description'>Your upgraded ships will be able to travel 30% faster than their original speed.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.hyperdrive5.name'>Hyperdrive v5</entry>
	<entry key='tech.hyperdrive5.longname'>Hyperdrive v5.0</entry>
	<entry key='tech.hyperdrive5.description'>High fuel consuption is the only disadvantage of this thruster system. It provides a 35% speed upgrade, with a 20% boost in maneuverability.</entry>
	
	<entry key='tech.ecm1.name'>ECM v1</entry>
	<entry key='tech.ecm1.longname'>ECM 1: "Fuzzbox"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.ecm1.description'>The Electronic Counter Measureme detects incoming missiles, and redirects them. The more time the ECM has to detect the missile, the more reliable it is.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.ecm2.name'>ECM v2</entry>
	<entry key='tech.ecm2.longname'>ECM 2: "Shocker"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.ecm2.description'>The Shocker ECM is an active countermeasures system. Using lasers, radio burst beams gravitic pulse fields and neutrino emitters it confuses and diverts missile attacks.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.storage1.name'>Cargo Pod</entry>
	<entry key='tech.storage1.longname'>Cargo Pod</entry>
	<entry key='tech.storage1.description'>This allows flagships to carry 3 additional ground vehicles.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.storage2.name'>Heavy Cargo Pod</entry>
	<entry key='tech.storage2.longname'>Heavy Cargo Pod</entry>
	<entry key='tech.storage2.description'>The Heavy Cargo Pod gives the flagship to which it is retrofitted room for an additional 5 ground vehicles.</entry>
	
	<entry key='tech.radar1.name'>Radar Array</entry>
	<entry key='tech.radar1.longname'>Radar Array</entry>
	<entry key='tech.radar1.description'>The Radar Array can be equipped onto any of your spaceships. It detects any ships within 2 parsecs.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.radar2.name'>Field Array</entry>
	<entry key='tech.radar2.longname'>Field Array</entry>
	<entry key='tech.radar2.description'>The Focused Field Radar Array can be equipped onto any of your spaceships. It detects any ships within 5 parsecs.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.radar3.name'>Phased Array</entry>
	<entry key='tech.radar3.longname'>Phased Array</entry>
	<entry key='tech.radar3.description'>The Phased Field Array is a series of tuned Radar Arrays which can be carried by a flagship, their combined power detects and identifies spaceships and planets as well.</entry>
	
	<entry key='tech.shield1.name'>Light Shield</entry>
	<entry key='tech.shield1.longname'>Light Shield</entry>
	<entry key='tech.shield1.description'>Using higher gauss mag-def fields than standard shields, this upgrade increases the shield strength of the ships by 10%.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.shield2.name'>Medium Shield</entry>
	<entry key='tech.shield2.longname'>Medium Shield</entry>
	<entry key='tech.shield2.description'>Also utilizing higher gauss mag-def fields this upgrade increases the shield power of ships by 15%.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.shield3.name'>Heavy Shield</entry>
	<entry key='tech.shield3.longname'>Heavy Shield</entry>
	<entry key='tech.shield3.description'>This unit upgrades the shield power by 20%. It uses a pulsed field technology.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.shield4.name'>SuperHvy Shield</entry>
	<entry key='tech.shield4.longname'>Super Heavy Shield</entry>
	<entry key='tech.shield4.description'>Like the Medium Shield, this is a redesign of the core mag-def technology. Pulsed EM fields upgrade the shield power of flagships by 25%.</entry>
	
	<entry key='tech.laser1.name'>Laser</entry>
	<entry key='tech.laser1.longname'>Laser</entry>
	<entry key='tech.laser1.description'>The Laser has been a common weapon since the early 21st century. Accurate and efficient its main drawback is its lack of damage dealing capability.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.laser2.name'>Pulse Laser</entry>
	<entry key='tech.laser2.longname'>Pulse Laser</entry>
	<entry key='tech.laser2.description'>The Pulse Laser is a simple upgrade, increasing the rate of fire, and thus the amount of energy delivered to the target ship.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.laser3.name'>UV Laser</entry>
	<entry key='tech.laser3.longname'>UV Laser</entry>
	<entry key='tech.laser3.description'>Advances in high wavelength focusing techniques allow the UV Laser to deliver significantly higher energy output, increasing the lethality of the weapon.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.laser4.name'>UV Pulse Laser</entry>
	<entry key='tech.laser4.longname'>UV Pulse Laser</entry>
	<entry key='tech.laser4.description'>Once the basic technique was perfected it was a simple step to upgrade the Pulse Laser to the focusing system. This is the most powerful laser available.</entry>
	
	<entry key='tech.ioncannon.name'>Ion Gun</entry>
	<entry key='tech.ioncannon.longname'>Ion Gun</entry>
	<entry key='tech.ioncannon.description'>the Ion Gun fires streams of positive and negatively charged ions. The two streams maintain cohesion until impact where the streams collapse in a huge blast.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.plasmacannon.name'>Plasma Gun</entry>
	<entry key='tech.plasmacannon.longname'>Plasma Gun</entry>
	<entry key='tech.plasmacannon.description'>The Plasma Gun fires a burst of superheated matter. A direct hit shatters hull plates with heat and shorts out electrical systems, crippling the target.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.particlecannon.name'>Neutron Gun</entry>
	<entry key='tech.particlecannon.longname'>Neutron Gun</entry>
	<entry key='tech.particlecannon.description'>The Neutron Gun is an improvement on the Ion Gun. Instead of charged ions it fires electrically neutral neutrons which increases beam cohesion and fire rate.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.mesoncannon.name'>Meson Gun</entry>
	<entry key='tech.mesoncannon.longname'>Meson Gun</entry>
	<entry key='tech.mesoncannon.description'>The ultimate weapon, the Meson Gun sprays short lived micro-singularities, easily crippling fleets of fighter craft.</entry>
	
	<entry key='tech.bomb1.name'>Bomb v1</entry>
	<entry key='tech.bomb1.longname'>Bomb v1.0: "Destructor""</entry>
	<entry key='tech.bomb1.description'>Destructors are used for attacking ground based targets from space. They are needed to take out ground based defenses.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.bomb2.name'>Bomb v2</entry>
	<entry key='tech.bomb2.longname'>Bomb v2.0: "Heavy Destructor""</entry>
	<entry key='tech.bomb2.description'>An improved destructor, it has a large blast radius and kills thousands of colony inhabitants if they are unprotected.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.virusbomb.name'>Virus bomb</entry>
	<entry key='tech.virusbomb.longname'>Virus bomb</entry>
	<entry key='tech.virusbomb.description'>The Virus bomb carries a payload of particularly virulent prions which are capable of killing all known lifeforms. After the planet is 'cleansed' the virus dies out.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.rocket1.name'>Missile v1</entry>
	<entry key='tech.rocket1.longname'>STK-1 Missile v1.0</entry>
	<entry key='tech.rocket1.description'>The STK-1 is a simple missile, carrying a high explosive load and using an uncomplicated turn and track targeting system. Maneuverability: 6  Speed: 500</entry>
	<entry key='tech.rocket2.name'>Missile v2</entry>
	<entry key='tech.rocket2.longname'>STK-1F Missile v2.0</entry>
	<entry key='tech.rocket2.description'>This new version of the STK-1 is more manuverable and faster. Manuverability: 8  Speed: 850</entry>
	<entry key='tech.multiheadedrocket.name'>Mul-head missile</entry>
	<entry key='tech.multiheadedrocket.longname'>Multi-head missile</entry>
	<entry key='tech.multiheadedrocket.description'>This missile when explodes will burst into small multi-head explosives, which clear a large area of fighter aircrafts.</entry>
	
	<entry key='tech.lighttank.name'>Light Tank</entry>
	<entry key='tech.lighttank.longname'>Light Tank: "Cougar"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.lighttank.description'>This Cougar Light Tank is often used as a recon vehicle due to its speed and armor. Fire range: 2, Speed: 5, Armor: 3</entry>
	<entry key='tech.mediumtank.name'>Medium Tank</entry>
	<entry key='tech.mediumtank.longname'>Medium Tank: "Tiger"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.mediumtank.description'>Trading speed for armor and range, the Tiger is a battlefield mainstay. Fire range: 4, Speed: 4, Armor: 4</entry>
	<entry key='tech.heavytank.name'>Heavy Tank</entry>
	<entry key='tech.heavytank.longname'>Heavy Tank: "Rhino"</entry>
	<entry key='tech.heavytank.description'>The Rhino Heavy Tank is the core of the Empire's ground forces. Fire range: 4  Speed: 4, Armour: 6</entry>
	<entry key='tech.behemoth.name'>Behemoth</entry>
	<entry key='tech.behemoth.longname'>Behemoth</entry>
	<entry key='tech.behemoth.description'>The Behemoth uses a spun-titanium weave armor plate for unparalleled defense. Fire range: 5, Speed: 3, Armor: 7</entry>
	
	<entry key='tech.radarcar.name'>Radar Car</entry>
	<entry key='tech.radarcar.longname'>Radar Car</entry>
	<entry key='tech.radarcar.description'>The Radar Car is a specialized recon vehicle with powerful side-looking radar, lidar, and magnetic detectors.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.rocketlauncher1.name'>Rocket Sled</entry>
	<entry key='tech.rocketlauncher1.longname'>Rocket Sled</entry>
	<entry key='tech.rocketlauncher1.description'>Vulnerable, but fast and agile, the Rocket Sled is a hit and run raider. Fire range: 7, Speed: 6.5, Armor: 2</entry>
	<entry key='tech.rocketlauncher2.name'>Hvy Rocket Sled</entry>
	<entry key='tech.rocketlauncher2.longname'>Heavy Rocket Sled</entry>
	<entry key='tech.rocketlauncher2.description'>The Heavy Rocket Sled sacrifices armor for speed and more powerful rockets. Fire range: 8, Speed: 7, Armor: 1</entry>
	
	<entry key='tech.solarplant.name'>Solar Plant</entry>
	<entry key='tech.solarplant.longname'>Solar Plant</entry>
	<entry key='tech.solarplant.description'>Advances in key technologies such as magnetohydrodynamics, optics, photovoltaics, and superconductors, are needed for the construction of this advanced power source.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.phoodfactory.name'>Phood(TM)Factory</entry>
	<entry key='tech.phoodfactory.longname'>Phood(TM) Factory</entry>
	<entry key='tech.phoodfactory.description'>With a few key breakthroughs in nanotechnology, genetic engineering, and marketing to sell the repulsive slop, the Phood(TM) Factory is an effective food source.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.tradecenter.name'>Trade center</entry>
	<entry key='tech.tradecenter.longname'>Trade center</entry>
	<entry key='tech.tradecenter.description'>The Trade center is a useful installation for increasing commerce, prosperity, and tax income on your colonies.</entry>
	
	<entry key='tech.inversionshield.name'>Inversion Shield</entry>
	<entry key='tech.inversionshield.longname'>Inversion Shield</entry>
	<entry key='tech.inversionshield.description'>The Inversion Shield consists of carefully balanced fields of gravitons with reversed spin, protecting your colony from Destructor fire from orbiting ships.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.hypershield.name'>Hyper Shield</entry>
	<entry key='tech.hypershield.longname'>Hyper Shield</entry>
	<entry key='tech.hypershield.description'>Utilizing the warping effects of millions of micro-singularities to absorb weapons fire, The Hyper shield protects your colony from Destructors and Virus Bombs.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fortress.name'>Fortress</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fortress.longname'>Fortress</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fortress.description'>The Fortress fires at nearby enemy vehicles. It also provides hangar bays and support equipment for your planetary garrisons.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.stronghold.name'>Stronghold</entry>
	<entry key='tech.stronghold.longname'>Stronghold</entry>
	<entry key='tech.stronghold.description'>The Stronghold is the heaviest fortification available for defending your colonies from ground based assaults.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.bunker.name'>Bunker</entry>
	<entry key='tech.bunker.longname'>Bunker</entry>
	<entry key='tech.bunker.description'>Bunkers are heavily reinforced structures which provide your colonists with a safe haven during attacks by enemy forces, greatly reducing casualties.</entry>
	
	<entry key='tech.radartelescope.name'>Radar Telescope</entry>
	<entry key='tech.radartelescope.longname'>Radar Telescope</entry>
	<entry key='tech.radartelescope.description'>The Radar Telescope detects nearby enemy fleets in space, helping to give warning before enemy attacks.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fieldtelescope.name'>Field Telescope</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fieldtelescope.longname'>Field Telescope</entry>
	<entry key='tech.fieldtelescope.description'>The Field Telescope is a high powered and focused radio wave detector that can be used to find enemy fleets at a greater range than the Radar Telescope.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.phasedtelescope.name'>Phased Telescope</entry>
	<entry key='tech.phasedtelescope.longname'>Phased Telescope</entry>
	<entry key='tech.phasedtelescope.description'>The Phased Telescope is the ultimate in long range sensing equipment, accurately locating enemy fleets at extreme ranges.</entry>
	
	<entry key='tech.plasmaprojector.name'>Plasma Projector</entry>
	<entry key='tech.plasmaprojector.longname'>Plasma Projector</entry>
	<entry key='tech.plasmaprojector.description'>Plasma Projector fires bolts of superheated matter that can inflict heavy damage on enemy starships.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.particleprojector.name'>Fusion Projector</entry>
	<entry key='tech.particleprojector.longname'>Fusion Projector</entry>
	<entry key='tech.particleprojector.description'>The Fusion Projector fires a magnetic bottle fusing hydrogen. It inflicts severe damage on enemy starships that stray into its range.</entry>
	<entry key='tech.mesonprojector.name'>Meson Projector</entry>
	<entry key='tech.mesonprojector.longname'>Meson Projector</entry>
	<entry key='tech.mesonprojector.description'>The Meson Projector fires a stream of subatomic particles that decay into highly explosive matter. These projectors can easily cripple an unsuspecting starship.</entry>
	
	<entry key='buildings.colony_hub.desc'>The colony hub is the prefabricated colony center automatically deposited on planet by a colonization ship. You can only build other structures on a planet if you have a colony hub.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.prefab_housing.desc'>Prefab housing is the cheapest low capacity housing available for your colonists. It comes in four exciting designer interior colors: puce, aquamarine, chiffon, and plaid.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.housing.upgrade_1'>Increase the capacity, the energy- and worker-demand to 125%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.housing.upgrade_2'>Increase the capacity, the energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.housing.upgrade_3'>Increase the capacity to 200%, the energy- and worker-demand to 175%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.housing.upgrade_4'>Increase the capacity to 250%, the energy to 200% and worker-demand to 175%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.apartment_block.desc'>Apartment blocks are more expensive to build than prefab housing but can provide living space for more people.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.arcology.desc'>Arcologies are expensive to build but allow the largest population of colonists per square meter.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.nuclear_plant.desc'>Nuclear Plants use the old-fashioned technology of atomic fission to generate power.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.power.upgrade_1'>Increase the output to 150%, the worker-demand to 125%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.power.upgrade_2'>Increase the output to 200%, the worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.power.upgrade_3'>Increase the output to 250%, the worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.power.upgrade_4'>Increase the output to 300%, the worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.fusion_plant.desc'>The Fusion Plant is most effective on planets with a ready supply of fusible materials (deuterium, tritium, helium-2). Buildable only on Earth-type and Icy planets.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.solar_plant.desc'>Advanced, super-efficient photovoltaics combined with high-temperature superconductors and orbital light focusing field arrays make Solar plants the most efficient power source.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.water_vaporator.desc'>Moisture Vaporators extract moisture from the air to provide drinking supplies. Water deficient planets need Vaporators to avoid slow population growth.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.hydroponic_food_farm.desc'>The Hydroponic Food Farm facility grows natural foods in an unnatural environment, extracting maximum yields from such exciting foodstuffs as grains, fungi, and algae.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.food.upgrade_1'>Increases the production, the energy- and worker-demand to 125%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.food.upgrade_2'>Increases the production, the energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.food.upgrade_3'>Increases the production, the energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.food.upgrade_4'>Increases the production to 250%, the energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.phood_factory.desc'>Phood(TM) Factory utilizes the latest advances in genetically engineered MeatBeast(TM), FastGrain(TM) and Sculpted Algae(TM) to produce large quantities of food for hungry colonists.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.spaceship_factory.desc'>The Spaceship factory increases the colony's spaceship production capacity.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.factory.upgrade_1'>Increases the capacity to 125%, the energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.factory.upgrade_2'>Increases the capacity to 150%, the energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.factory.upgrade_3'>Increases the capacity to 175%, the energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.factory.upgrade_4'>Increases the capacity to 200%, the energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.equipment_factory.desc'>The Equipment factory increases the colony's equipment production capacity.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.weapon_factory.desc'>The Weapon factory increases the colony's weapon production capacity.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.civil_dev_center.desc'>The Civil Engineering Development Center increases your colony's knowledge of Civil Engineering, which increases your Development capabilities.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.science.upgrade_1'>Decrease the energy- and worker-demand to 75%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.science.upgrade_2'>Decrease the energy- and worker-demand to 50%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.science.upgrade_3'>Decrease the energy- and worker-demand to 25%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.science.upgrade_4'>Decrease the energy- and worker-demand to 5%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.mechanical_dev_center.desc'>The Mechanics Development Center increases your colony's knowledge of Mechanics, which increases your Development capabilities.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.computer_dev_center.desc'>The Computer Development Center increases your colony's knowledge of Computer Technology, which increases your Development capabilities.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.ai_dev_center.desc'>The AI Development Center increases your colony's knowledge of Artificial Intelligence, which increases your Development capabilities.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.military_dev_center.desc'>The Military Development Center increases your colony's knowledge of Military Technology, which increases your Development capabilities.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.traders_spaceport.desc'>Integrated commercial spaceports, automated customs processing facilities, robot dockworkers and the Spacemerchant's Guild make the Traders' spaceport a valuable revenue source.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.traders_spaceport.upgrade_1'>Increase the credit income, the energy- and worker-demand to 125%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.traders_spaceport.upgrade_2'>Increase the credit income, the energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.traders_spaceport.upgrade_3'>Increase the credit income, the energy- and worker-demand to 175%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.traders_spaceport.upgrade_4'>Increase the credit income to 200%, the energy- and worker-demand to 175%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.military_spaceport.desc'>Military spaceports allow the construction and support of military spaceships. They also can provide some local System Defense Boats to aid in protecting the colony from attacks.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.bank.desc'>Banks provide financial investments for local commerce increasing trade and income on the colony.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.bank.upgrade_1'>Increase the commerce to 2.5-times, the energy- and worker-demand to 125%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.bank.upgrade_2'>Increase the commerce to 3-times, the energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.bank.upgrade_3'>Increase the commerce to 3.5-times, the energy- and worker-demand to 175%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.bank.upgrade_4'>Increase the commerce to 4-times, the energy- and worker-demand to 175%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.trade_center.desc'>The trade center forms the hub of colonial commerce, the presence of one increases weekly trade income.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.trade_center.upgrade_1'>Increase the credit income, the energy- and worker-demand to 125%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.trade_center.upgrade_2'>Increase the credit income, the energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.trade_center.upgrade_3'>Increase the credit income, the energy- and worker-demand to 175%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.trade_center.upgrade_4'>Increase the credit income to 200%, the energy- and worker-demand to 175%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.hospital.desc'>Hospitals improve colony morale and health, fight disease and find solutions to the challenges of life on alien planets allowing the population to grow more quickly.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.hospital.upgrade_1'>Increase the capacity to 125%, the energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.hospital.upgrade_2'>Increase the capacity to 150%, the energy- and worker-demand to 175%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.hospital.upgrade_3'>Increase the capacity to 175%, the energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.hospital.upgrade_4'>Increase the capacity to 200%, the energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.police_station.desc'>Police Stations are demanded by the colonists on sufficiently populated worlds to reduce crime to acceptable levels.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.police_station.upgrade_1'>Increase the coverage to 125%, the energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.police_station.upgrade_2'>Increase the coverage to 150%, the energy- and worker-demand to 175%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.police_station.upgrade_3'>Increase the coverage to 175%, the energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.police_station.upgrade_4'>Increase the coverage to 200%, the energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.fire_brigade.desc'>Fire brigades automatically repair damaged colony structures up to 50%- free of charge. They are very useful when a colony is being bombarded from orbit or assaulted by ground forces.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.fire_brigade.upgrade_1'>Increase the repair to 55%, the energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.fire_brigade.upgrade_2'>Increase the repair to 61%, the energy- and worker-demand to 175%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.fire_brigade.upgrade_3'>Increase the repair to 68%, the energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.fire_brigade.upgrade_4'>Increase the repair to 77%, the energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.radar_telescope.desc'>The Radar Telescope detects nearby enemy fleets in space, helping to give warning before enemy attacks.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.field_telescope.desc'>The Field Telescope is a high powered and focused radio wave detector that can be used to find enemy fleets at a greater range than the Radar Telescope.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.phased_telescope.desc'>The Phased Telescope is the ultimate in long range sensing equipment, accurately pinpointing enemy fleet positions at extreme ranges.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.bunker.desc'>The Bunker is a heavily reinforced concrete and neo-titanium bomb shelter that the civilian population retreats to when the colony is attacked, reducing deaths in orbital/ground assaults.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.bunker.upgrade_1'>Decrease war losses by 55%, the energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.bunker.upgrade_2'>Decrease war losses by 61%, the energy- and worker-demand to 175%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.bunker.upgrade_3'>Decrease war losses by 68%, the energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.bunker.upgrade_4'>Decrease war losses by 77%, the energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.ion_projector.desc'>The Ion Projector is used to protect your colony from attack by enemy starfleets. It fires a stream of high energy charged particles that can damage most enemy ships.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.ion_projector.upgrade_1'>Increase the firepower to 115%, the energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.ion_projector.upgrade_2'>Increase the firepower to 130%, the energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.ion_projector.upgrade_3'>Increase the firepower to 145%, the energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.ion_projector.upgrade_4'>Increase the firepower to 160%, the energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.plasma_projector.desc'>Plasma projectors fire bolts of superheated matter that can inflict heavy damage on enemy starships.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.plasma_projector.upgrade_1'>Increase the firepower to 115%, the energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.plasma_projector.upgrade_2'>Increase the firepower to 130%, the energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.plasma_projector.upgrade_3'>Increase the firepower to 145%, the energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.plasma_projector.upgrade_4'>Increase the firepower to 160%, the energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.fusion_projector.desc'>Getting hit by a shot from a Fusion Projector is like running into a small sun. It inflicts severe damage on enemy starships that stray into its range.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.fusion_projector.upgrade_1'>Increase the firepower to 115%, the energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.fusion_projector.upgrade_2'>Increase the firepower to 130%, the energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.fusion_projector.upgrade_3'>Increase the firepower to 145%, the energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.fusion_projector.upgrade_4'>Increase the firepower to 160%, the energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.meson_projector.desc'>The Meson Projector fires a stream of subatomic particles that decay into highly explosive matter. These projectors can easily cripple an unsuspecting starship with a single blast.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.meson_projector.upgrade_1'>Increase the firepower to 115%, the energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.meson_projector.upgrade_2'>Increase the firepower to 130%, the energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.meson_projector.upgrade_3'>Increase the firepower to 145%, the energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.meson_projector.upgrade_4'>Increase the firepower to 160%, the energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.inversion_shield.desc'>The Inversion Shield consists of carefully balanced fields of gravitons with reversed spin, which form a highly repulsive barrier around your colony protecting from attacks from space.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.inversion_shield.upgrade_1'>Increase the shield to 60%, the energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.inversion_shield.upgrade_2'>Increase the shield to 70%, the energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.inversion_shield.upgrade_3'>Increase the shield to 80%, the energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.inversion_shield.upgrade_4'>Increase the shield to 90%, the energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.hypershield.desc'>Utilizing the warping effects of millions of micro-singularities to absorb weapons fire, The Hyper shield protects your colony from Destructors and Virus Bombs.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.hypershield.upgrade_1'>Increase the shield to 60%, the energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.hypershield.upgrade_2'>Increase the shield to 70%, the energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.hypershield.upgrade_3'>Increase the shield to 80%, the energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.hypershield.upgrade_4'>Increase the shield to 90%, the energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.barracks.desc'>The Barracks is the simplest fortifications available. During a ground assault it will fire on nearby enemy tanks and allows you to house four tanks of your own for defense.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.barracks.upgrade_1'>Increse the firepower, the energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.barracks.upgrade_2'>Increse the firepower, the energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.fortress.desc'>The Fortress greatly improves your colony's defenses against ground assaults. It fires are enemy tanks and has storage space for eight of your own defensive tanks.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.fortress.upgrade_1'>Increse the firepower, the energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.fortress.upgrade_2'>Increse the firepower, the energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.stronghold.desc'>The Stronghold is the heaviest fortification you can build to defend your colony against ground attacks. It fires at nearby enemy tanks and provides hangar bays for twelve tanks.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.recreation_center.desc'>The Recreation center provides such healthy entertainments as Hyperpool, FlashPong, and Billiards. These entertainments improve morale on the colony.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.recreation_center.upgrade_1'>Increase the morale by 6%, energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.recreation_center.upgrade_2'>Increase the morale by 7%, energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.recreation_center.upgrade_3'>Increase the morale by 8%, energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.recreation_center.upgrade_4'>Increase the morale by 9%, energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.park.desc'>Parks provide a physical reminder of the colonists homeworld. These pleasant, relaxing oasises of faux-nature raise colony morale.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.park.upgrade_1'>Increase the morale by 12%, energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.park.upgrade_2'>Increase the morale by 14%, energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.park.upgrade_3'>Increase the morale by 16%, energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.park.upgrade_4'>Increase the morale by 18%, energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.church.desc'>Spiritual Indoctrination Centers, Churches foster the belief in an ephemeral spiritual reward for worldly suffering, increasing colony morale at very low cost.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.church.upgrade_1'>Increase the morale by 12%, energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.church.upgrade_2'>Increase the morale by 14%, energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.church.upgrade_3'>Increase the morale by 16%, energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.church.upgrade_4'>Increase the morale by 18%, energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.bar.desc'>A social space where colonists bond with one another through the shared ritual consumption of perception altering substances such as NeoPro Brandy, bars raise colony morale.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.bar.upgrade_1'>Increase the morale by 15%, energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.bar.upgrade_2'>Increase the morale by 18%, energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.bar.upgrade_3'>Increase the morale by 21%, energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.bar.upgrade_4'>Increase the morale by 24%, energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.stadium.desc'>The stadium provides a location for performances and sporting events to be put on for the colonists. Full Contact Arcturian Rules Football has proven very effective at raising morale.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.stadium.upgrade_1'>Increase the morale by 24%, energy- and worker-demand to 150%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.stadium.upgrade_2'>Increase the morale by 28%, energy- and worker-demand to 200%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.stadium.upgrade_3'>Increase the morale by 32%, energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	<entry key='buildings.stadium.upgrade_4'>Increase the morale by 36%, energy- and worker-demand to 250%.</entry>
	
	<entry key='buildinginfo.building.cost'  >Cost   : %d cr</entry>
	<entry key='buildinginfo.building.energy'>Energy : %d kWh</entry>
	<entry key='buildinginfo.building.worker'>Worker : %d</entry>
	<entry key='buildinginfo.planet.surface'>%s surface</entry>
	
	<entry key='colonyinfo.population.short.alien'>%d alien</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.population.own'>%d %s %s</entry>
	
	<entry key='financialinfo.yesterday'>Yesterday</entry>
	<entry key='financialinfo.today'>Today</entry>
	<entry key='financialinfo.production_cost'>Production cost : %d cr</entry>
	<entry key='financialinfo.research_cost'  >Research cost   : %d cr</entry>
	<entry key='financialinfo.repair_cost'    >Repair cost     : %d cr</entry>
	<entry key='financialinfo.build_cost'     >Build cost      : %d cr</entry>
	
	<entry key='researchinfo.progress.done'>Done</entry>
	<entry key='researchinfo.progress.running'>Running: %d%%</entry>
	<entry key='researchinfo.progress.paused'>Paused: %d%%</entry>
	<entry key='researchinfo.progress.money'>Money shortage: %d%%</entry>
	<entry key='researchinfo.progress.lab'>Cap. shortage: %d%%</entry>
	<entry key='researchinfo.progress.can'>Researchable</entry>
	<entry key='researchinfo.progress.cant'>Not researchable</entry>
	<entry key='researchinfo.progress.inventory'>Inventory : %d</entry>
	<entry key='researchinfo.progress.cost'     >Cost      : %d cr</entry>
	<entry key='researchinfo.progress.price'    >Price     : %d cr</entry>
	<entry key='researchinfo.progress.pre'      >Prerequisites:</entry>
	<entry key='colonyinfo.tax_short'>Tax: %s</entry>
	<entry key='researchinfo.required_labs'>Required / Available:</entry>
	
	<entry key='info.list_details'>Details</entry>
	<entry key='info.hide_details'>List</entry>
	<entry key='info.population_details'>Population</entry>
	<entry key='info.morale_details'>Morale</entry>
	<entry key='info.problem_details'>Problems</entry>
	
	<entry key='statistics.total_pause_time'>Total pause time</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.money_tax_income'>Tax income</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.money_trade_income'>Trade income</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.money_demolish_income'>Demolish income</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.money_sell_income'>Sell income</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.money_spent_repair'>Money for repair</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.money_spent_upgade'>Money for upgrade</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.build_count'>Build count</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.demolish_count'>Demolish count</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.sell_count'>Sell count</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.production_count'>Production count</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.upgrade_count'>Upgrade count</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.planet_conquered'>Planet conquered</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_money_aquired'>Galaxy total money income</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_money_tax_income'>Galaxy total tax income</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_money_trade_income'>Galaxy total trade income</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_money_demolish_income'>Galaxy demolish income</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_money_sell_income'>Galaxy sell income</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_money_spent_building'>Galaxy spent on buildings</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_money_spent_repair'>Galaxy spent on repair</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_money_spent_production'>Galaxy spent on production</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_money_spent_research'>Galaxy spent on research</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_money_spent_upgade'>Galaxy spent on upgrade</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_build_count'>Galaxy build count</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_demolish_count'>Galaxy demolish count</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_sell_count'>Galaxy sell count</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_production_count'>Galaxy production count</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_research_count'>Galaxy research count</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_upgrade_count'>Galaxy upgrade count</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_actual_buildings'>Galaxy operational buildings</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_total_food_production'>Galaxy total food production</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_money_tax_income'>Galaxy tax income</entry>
	<entry key='statistics.galaxy_money_trade_income'>Galaxy trade income</entry>
	<entry key='info.statistics'>Statistics</entry>
	
	<entry key='relations.allies'>Allies:</entry>
	<entry key='relations.enemies'>Enemies:</entry>
	
	<entry key='newfleet.name'>New Fleet</entry>
	<entry key='fleetstatus.stopped'>Stopped</entry>
	<entry key='fleetstatus.stopped.at'>Stopped near %s</entry>
	<entry key='fleetstatus.attack'>Attacking %s</entry>
	<entry key='fleetstatus.moving'>Moving</entry>
	<entry key='fleetstatus.moving.to'>Moving to %s</entry>
	<entry key='fleetstatus.moving.after'>Following %s</entry>
	<entry key='fleetstatus.composition'>Battleships:%s Cruisers:%s Fighters: %s Tanks:%s</entry>
	<entry key='fleetstatus.firepower'>Firepower: %d</entry>
	<entry key='fleetstatus.speed'    >Speed    : %d</entry>
	<entry key='fleetstatus.nearby'>Planet near by: %s</entry>
	
	<entry key='inventoryslot.laser'>Lasers</entry>
	<entry key='inventoryslot.laser1'>Lasers</entry>
	<entry key='inventoryslot.laser2'>Lasers</entry>
	<entry key='inventoryslot.shield'>Shield</entry>
	<entry key='inventoryslot.hyperdrive'>Hyperdrive</entry>
	<entry key='inventoryslot.radar'>Radar</entry>
	<entry key='inventoryslot.cannon'>Cannons</entry>
	<entry key='inventoryslot.cannon1'>Cannons</entry>
	<entry key='inventoryslot.cannon2'>Cannons</entry>
	<entry key='inventoryslot.bomb'>Bombs</entry>
	<entry key='inventoryslot.rocket'>Rockets</entry>
	<entry key='inventoryslot.rocket1'>Rockets</entry>
	<entry key='inventoryslot.rocket2'>Rockets</entry>
	<entry key='inventoryslot.storage'>Storage</entry>
	<entry key='inventoryslot.ecm'>ECM</entry>
	
	<entry key='fleetinformation.battleships'>Battleships: %s</entry>
	<entry key='fleetinformation.cruisers'   >Cruisers   : %s</entry>
	<entry key='fleetinformation.fighters'   >Fighters   : %s</entry>
	<entry key='fleetinformation.vehicles'   >Vehicles   : %s</entry>
	
	<entry key='info.empty-list'>None</entry>
	<entry key='production.needs_orbital_factory'>Orbital Factory</entry>
	
	<entry key='load'>Load</entry>
	<entry key='save'>Save</entry>
	<entry key='settings'>Settings</entry>
	<entry key='mainmenu'>Main menu</entry>
	<entry key='delete'>Delete</entry>
	<entry key='no_saves'>No saves available</entry>
	<entry key='load_save'>Load / Save</entry>
	
	<entry key='info.planet_name'>Planet</entry>
	
	<entry key='settings.sound_volume'>Sound volume</entry>
	<entry key='settings.music_volume'>Music volume</entry>
	<entry key='settings.video_volume'>Video volume</entry>
	<entry key='settings.reequip_tanks'>Reequip tanks after battle</entry>
	<entry key='settings.reequip_bombs'>Reequip bombs/rockets after battle</entry>
	<entry key='settings.computer_voice'>Computer voice</entry>
	<entry key='settings.autobuild_limit'>Auto-Build credit limit</entry>
	<entry key=''></entry>
	<entry key=''></entry>
	<entry key=''></entry>
	
</labels>